<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FragmentsDemo</string>

    <string-array name="countries">
        <item>India</item>
        <item>USA</item>
        <item>Pakistan</item>
        <item>Bangladesh</item>
        <item>Egypt</item>
        <item>Indonesia</item>
        <item>UK</item>
        <item>Germany</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="India">
        India is a vast South Asian country with diverse terrain – from Himalayan peaks to Indian Ocean coastline – and history reaching back 5 millennia.
        In the north, Mughal Empire landmarks include Delhi\’s Red Fort complex and massive Jama Masjid mosque, plus Agra’s iconic Taj Mahal mausoleum.
        Pilgrims bathe in the Ganges in Varanasi, and Rishikesh is a yoga centre and base for Himalayan trekking.
    </string>
    <string name="USA">
        The U.S. is a country of 50 states covering a vast swath of North America, with Alaska in the northwest and Hawaii extending the nation\’s
        presence into the Pacific Ocean. Major Atlantic Coast cities are New York, a global finance and culture center, and capital Washington, DC.
        Midwestern metropolis Chicago is known for influential architecture and on the west coast, Los Angeles\' Hollywood is famed for filmmaking.
    </string>
    <string name="Pakistan">
        Pakistan, officially the Islamic Republic of Pakistan, is a country in South Asia and on junction of West Asia, Central Asia and East Asia.
        It is the fifth-most populous country with a population exceeding 209,970,000 people.
    </string>
    <string name="Bangladesh">
        Bangladesh, to the east of India on the Bay of Bengal, is a South Asian country marked by lush greenery and many waterways.
        Its Padma (Ganges), Meghna and Jamuna rivers create fertile plains, and travel by boat is common. On the southern coast, the Sundarbans,
        an enormous mangrove forest shared with Eastern India, is home to the royal Bengal tiger.
    </string>
    <string name="Egypt">
        Egypt, a country linking northeast Africa with the Middle East, dates to the time of the pharaohs. Millennia-old monuments sit along the
        fertile Nile River Valley, including Giza\'s colossal Pyramids and Great Sphinx as well as Luxor\'s hieroglyph-lined Karnak Temple and
        Valley of the Kings tombs. The capital, Cairo, is home to Ottoman landmarks like Muhammad Ali Mosque and the Egyptian Museum, a trove of antiquities.
    </string>
    <string name="Indonesia">
        Indonesia, a Southeast Asian nation made up of thousands of volcanic islands, is home to hundreds of ethnic groups speaking many different languages.
        It\’s known for beaches, volcanoes, Komodo dragons and jungles sheltering elephants, orangutans and tigers. On the island of Java lies Indonesia\'s
        vibrant, sprawling capital, Jakarta, and the city of Yogyakarta, known for gamelan music and traditional puppetry.
    </string>
    <string name="UK">
        The United Kingdom, made up of England, Scotland, Wales and Northern Ireland, is an island nation in northwestern Europe.
        England – birthplace of Shakespeare and The Beatles – is home to the capital, London, a globally influential centre of finance and culture.
        England is also site of Neolithic Stonehenge, Bath’s Roman spa and centuries-old universities at Oxford and Cambridge.
    </string>
    <string name="Germany">
        Germany is a Western European country with a landscape of forests, rivers, mountain ranges and North Sea beaches.
        It has over 2 millennia of history. Berlin, its capital, is home to art and nightlife scenes, the Brandenburg Gate and many sites relating to WWII.
        Munich is known for its Oktoberfest and beer halls, including the 16th-century Hofbräuhaus. Frankfurt, with its skyscrapers,
        houses the European Central Bank.
    </string>
</resources>
